{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Kāixué" ,
      "answer": "开学"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kāi",
      "answer": "开"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hěn" ,
      "answer": "很"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gāoxìng",
      "answer": "高兴"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gāo",
      "answer": "高"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kàn",
      "answer": "看"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wèn",
      "answer": "问"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīxià",
      "answer": "一下"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuéyuàn",
      "answer": "学院"
    },
    {
      "question": "Míngpiàn",
      "answer": "名片"
    },
    {
      "question": "à",
      "answer": "啊"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiàoshòu",
      "answer": "教授"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiào",
      "answer": "教"
    }
  ]
}
